CHAIYONG RAGKHITWETSAGUL

CREST, Department of Computer Science University College London, Gower Street, London, UK chaiyong.ragkhitwetsagul.14@ucl.ac.uk cragkhit.github.io

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am currently a 4th-year PhD student in the Centre for Research on Evolution, Search and Testing (CREST), Department of Computer Science, University College London. I am also an assistant instructor at the Faculty of ICT, Mahidol University who is the main sponsor for my PhD study.

CURRENT **PROJECTS**

CloneNets: Detecting code clones in JavaScript using recurrent neural networks. Cloverflow: An empirical study of toxic code snippets on Stack Overflow

- PUBLICATIONS J. Wilkie, Z. Al Halabi, A. Karaoglu, J. Liao, G. Ndungu, C. Ragkhitwetsagul, M. Paixo, J. Krinke (2018). Who's this? Developer identification using IDE event data. In the 15th International Conference on Mining Software Repositories - Mining Challenge (MSR 2018), 2018. Gothenburg, Sweden
 - C. Ragkhitwetsagul, J. Krinke (2018). A picture is worth a thousand words: code clone detection based on image similarity. In the 12th International Workshop on Software Clones (IWSC 2018), 2018. Campobasso, Italy – The People's Choice Award
 - C. Ragkhitwetsagul, J. Krinke, R. Oliveto (2017). Awareness and Experience of Developers to Outdated and License-Violating Code on Stack Overflow: An Online Survey. UCL Computer Science Research Note (RN/17/10), 2017.
 - C. Ragkhitwetsagul, J. Krinke, D.Clark (2017). A Comparison of Code Similarity Analysers. Empirical Software Engineering, https://doi.org/10.1007/s10664-017-9564-7, 2017.
 - M. Paixao, J. Krinke, D. Han, C. Ragkhitwetsagul and M. Harman (2017). Are Developers Aware of the Architectural Impact of Their Changes?. In the 32nd IEEE/ACM International Conference on Automated Software Engineering (ASE 2017), 2017. Illinois, USA
 - C. Ragkhitwetsagul, J. Krinke (2017). Using Compilation/Decompilation to Enhance Clone Detection. In 11th International Workshop on Software Clones, 2017. Klagenfurt, Austria - The People's Choice Award
 - C. Ragkhitwetsagul, M. Paixao, M. Adham, S. Busari, J. Krinke, and J. H. Drake (2016). Searching for Configurations in Clone Evalution: A Replication Study. In 8th International Symposium on Search-based Software Engineering (SSBSE): Challenge Track, 2016. Raleigh, NC, USA. (NSF Student Travel Support)
 - C. Ragkhitwetsagul, J. Krinke, D. Clark (2016). Similarity of Source Code in the Presence of Pervasive Modifications. In 16th IEEE International Working Conference on Source Code Analysis and Manipulation (SCAM), 2016. Raleigh, NC, USA.
 - C. Ragkhitwetsagul (2016). Measuring Code Similarity in Large-scaled Code Corpora. In 32nd International Conference on Software Maintenance and Evolution (ICSME): Doctoral Symposium, 2016. Raleigh, NC, USA.

P. Janviriya, T. Ongarjithichai, P. Numruktrakul, C. Ragkhitwetsagul. (2014). *Cloudy-Days : Cloud Storage Integration System.* In ICT-ISPC 2014 (pp. 125-128). Nakhonpathom, Thailand.

P. Hathaiwichian, L. Siriwittayacharoen, A. Wongwachirawanich, C. Ragkhitwetsagul (2014). Android Application for Event Management and Information Propagation. In ICT-ISPC 2014 (pp. 139-142). Nakhonpathom, Thailand.

EDUCATION

2014 - Present, PhD

PhD in Computer Science

University College London, UK Research topic: Online code cloning

Supervisors: Dr. Jens Krinke, Dr. David Clark

Research interest: code clone/plagiarism detection, code similarity, mining of software

repositories, search-based software engineering

2007 - 2008, Master

Master of Science in IT – Very Large Information Systems

Carnegie Mellon University, USA

Capstone project: Honeydew – Meeting date prediction using machine learning

2002 - 2005, Undergraduate

Bachelor Degree in Computer Engineering (Magna cum Laude)

Kasetsart University, Thailand

AWARDS

The People's Choice Award

2018

A picture is worth a thousand words: code clone detection based on image similarity IWSC 2018. Campobasso, Italy.

The People's Choice Award

2017

Using Compilation/Decompilation to Enhance Clone Detection

IWSC 2017. Klagenfurt, Austria.

NSF Student Travel Support (700 USD)

2016

SSBSE 2016. Raleigh, NC, USA.

Microsoft Azure Research Award (20,000 USD)

2016

ISiCS: Internet-scaled Similar Code Search project

Full PhD scholarship

2014 -2018

 $Mahidol\ University\ A cademic\ Development\ Scholarship$

& Faculty of ICT, Mahidol University Scholarship

2008

Best Project Award: 15-637 Web App Development, Carnegie Mellon University

WhimsyWord: multi-player online hangman game

Full Master degree scholarship

2007 - 2008

The Royal Thai Government scholarship

Winner of the 8th National Software Contest of Thailand (NSC)

2006

Category - Software for Entertainment

Sword Edge: virtual reality fighting game

2005

DTAC & NOKIA i-Awards mobile app contest: finalists

Interactive e-cards mobile application

EXPERIENCE

Research Student

Sep 2014 - Present

Centre for Research on Evolution, Search and Testing (CREST),

Software Systems Engineering (SSE) group,

Department of Computer Science, University College London

Conducting research in code similarity, code reuse, code clone/plagiarism detection, and search-based software engineering

Assistant Instructor

Dec 2012 - Sep 2014

Faculty of ICT, Mahidol University, Nakhonpathom, Thailand

Lectured Fundamentals of Programming, OOP, DBMS, Knowledge-based Systems, and Mobile App Development.

Advised three undergraduate student projects.

Consultant Nov 2011 - Sep 2014

Blaccess Thailand

Made key decisions and providing company's vision.

Planned and managed IT projects and staffs.

System Analyst Jan 2009 - Nov 2012

National Economic and Social Development Board, Thailand

Planned, maintained, and developed NESDB IT services (e.g. email systems, web applications, DBMS).

Administrated NESDB applications and computer networks.

Teacher Feb 2010 - Dec 2012

ProGaming, Thailand

Instructed Pro Android course on developing Android applications.

Instructed Pro iOS course on developing iOS applications.

Developer Jan 2009 - Dec 2012

Kasetsart University, Thailand

Developed a digital repository, and training/project tracking system for Puparn Royal Development Study Center.

Intern Mar 2008 - Aug 2008

Oracle, USA

Developed of a new version of Oracle's internal testing platform, Distributed Testing System (DTS) 2.0, using Java web technology and Javascript.

Software Test Engineer

Feb 2006 - Apr 2007

Microsoft, Thailand

Created automated test tools for testing localized versions of Windows Vista User Assistance Platform.

Tested user assistance (UA) contents in XML format.

SKILLS Platforms: macOS, Linux, Windows, Raspberry Pi, iOS, Android

Programming languages: Python, Shell scripts, Java, C/C++, Obj-C, SQL

PROFESSIONAL Publicity Chair: IWSC 2018

Mar 2018

ACTIVITIES Reviewer: JSS (Nov 2017), IET (Oct 2017), STVR (Apr 2017), PeerJ Computer Sci-

ence (May 2016)

Subreviewer: MSR '18, REVE'17, ICSME'17, MSR'17, IWSC'17, SANER'17, SCAM'16,

SCAM'15

REFERENCES References upon request.